Hello Hello!
We are at Gröna Lund!
- We are entirely ourselves inside the amusement park.
- All themselves.
It's so cool.
It's so quiet, it's so quiet.
- (Alma) It's so ... oooh ... - It's a little mysterious almost.
It feels a bit jerky.
All Jalusians are pulled out ...
(Alma) Oh, that little ... the thing.
It's completely empty, and it's just ... It's a little scary.
- No, it's pretty good!
- Yes.
This is going to be super fun.
The park will open, and then we will stay and go stuff.
So Gröna Lund let us in before opening, so we can experience the park "All Alone".
Here they play music.
- Do you get a feeling?
- Yes.
- Do you dance with the carriage?
I try to.
May I be allowed, Pipita?
She dances with the pacifier.
Yes, she thought the pacifier was more fun.
- Here you will get, Björn.
Pew, Pew, Pew!
- (a siren -like sound is heard)
- What is the sound?
- I do not know.
Was it ... some kind of monster that I have to shoot?
Where!
There are monsters.
News of the year.
It is also the ride we will go first today.